# MORGAN KIGER

Software Development Intern | www.morgankiger.com

#### • DETAILS •

www.morgankiger.com kiger@unlv.nevada.edu

• LINKS •

LinkedIn

Github

o SKILLS o

Linux/Command Prompt
SQL Database
Efficient Time Management
Requires Minimal Supervision
Creative Thinker
Agile Methodologies

### PROFILE

Capable and adaptable college student with a focus on IT. A quick learner and self-motivated to learn new technology and better problem solving skills. Worked in data entry, sat in important meetings with partners and provided feedback, coded scripts in python, extracted data from a database and compared results, and even lead projects and took leadership roles.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

# Software Development Intern at Bonotel Exlcusive Travel

October 2019 - Present

- Coded automation for data entry process within the business
- Automated inventory check of all active hotels
- Built a status page for applications the business uses
- · Built reports by pulling data from databases

### IT Intern at Bonotel Exclusive Travel

December 2015 - October 2018

- Mapped hotels to our system, to create a real-time connection for rates
- Supported all of internal staff with anything tech related

## Guest Services/Reservations Agent at Bonotel Exclusive Travel

April 2015 - December 2015

- Handled customer issues in a gracious manner and in accordance with company policies.
- Answered phone calls, liaison between hotel and partner, sold/booked hotel rooms

# Shift Manager at Sweet Addiction

August 2012 - May 2014

- Supervised staff and handled all customer service issues
- Handled all money/till at the end of the day, ultimately ran the shop

# EDUCATION

### University of Nevada Las Vegas

August 2014 - Present

Degree: Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

- Minor in Computer Science and Mathematics
- Member of Lambda Chi Alpha
  - Held position: President, Secretary, Alumni Relations

# West Career & Technical Academy

August 2010 - May 2014

**Degree: Business Management** 

- Advanced Honors Dipolma
- Competed in Future Business Leaders of America's National Competition for two years.
   Received an award for placing 3rd.